Ahmed Mohamed

Frontend Developer

Hi, I am Ahmed Mohamed an energetic and enthusiastic frontend web developer eager to learn new technologies and build amazing stuff. I'm 30 years old, up I am enjoying building elegant and professional web pages in a modern way. I have developed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Reactjs, Nodejs (nest) and other skills to help me fulfill high qualifications and Finished Military Service in Mar 2017.

Work History

2021-12 -Current

Frontend Developer

AFAQY, Cairo

- Make app live tracking to help track the vehicles on your system using leaflet map
- create automatic systems to locate the car that you do some of the work assigned to it according to the business
- · Unit testing with (Karma or jest)
- · Create projects with angular +10 or Reactjs
- Made recommendations for new technology integration based on suitability and alignment to business goals.
- · Responsibility For Restful APIs

2021-02 -2023-12

Frontend Developer

El-Dokan software, Cairo

- Work on projects related to e-commerce like (Masr pharmacy | Zahranstores | Mobilaty | Switchplus eg)
- Unit testing with (Karma or jest)
- Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs (Next is)
- Responsibility For Restful APIs
- · Performance And Usability Testing

2019-04 -2021-01

Frontend Developer

Proemcs, Cairo

- · Create projects related to the medical field
- Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs
- Work on projects related to medical field
- · Responsibility For Restful APIs
- · Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

2018-01 -2019-03

Frontend Developer

Valux Apps, Cairo

- · Create projects with angular +7 or Reactjs
- · Responsibility For Restful APIs
- Performance And Usability Testing
- Convert PSD | | ProtoType To PugJS & SCSS

Education

2011-09 -2015-06

System And Information With Bachelor Degree

Cairo Higher Institutes - Cairo, Egypt
I'm a graduated system and information with
Bachelor's degree, Mokattam I've Learning At Cairo
Higher Institutes HTML, FrontPage, Economic,
Marketing, Feasibility Study, Information Security,
Network Security

Contact

Address

Cairo Egypt

Phone

01124269532

E-mail

ahmed.m.moneem@gmail.

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/iahmedmohamed

www

https://ahmedmohamed26 .github.io

Skills

Angular +7

Reactis

Rxjs

Redux

Nodejs (nest)

Typescript

Javascript

Nx (workspace)

Git

Scss

MUI (Angular, React)

HTML5

CSS3